<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!--
   New Perspectives on XML 3rd Edition
   Tutorial 6
   Review Assignment

   Harpe Gaming Store Board Games
   Author: Rob Walczak
   Date:   03/20/2017

   Filename:         games.xml
   Supporting Files: games.xsl
   
   games
       |__game (gid)
          |__title
          |__manufacturer
          |__price
          |__releaseDate
          |__media
          |__age
          |__players
          |__time
          |__image 
          |__summary
          |  |__h3
          |  |__p
          |  |__i
          |__scores
             |__score (category)
-->
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="faq.xsl" ?>

<FAQs>
   <FAQ qid="Q1">
      <question>FAQ</question>
	  <summary>
		<p><i> How far in advance do I have to book a flight?</i></p>
		<p> We recommend to book a flight at least 2 weeks in advance for a guaranteed flight.</p>
	  </summary>
   </FAQ>
   
   <FAQ qid="Q1">
	  <summary>
		<p><i> Where can I see my bids for flights?</i></p>
		<p> You can check your current bids on your account page.</p>
	  </summary>
   </FAQ>
   
   <FAQ qid="Q1">
	  <summary>
		<p><i> Do I have to pay for the pilot and the stewardess?</i></p>
		<p> The owner of the plane will provide the both the pilot and stewardess</p>
	  </summary>
   </FAQ>
   
   <FAQ qid="Q1">
	  <summary>
		<p><i> How do I put my plane up for use?</i></p>
		<p> You send us your information and we will have the plane inspected for use.</p>
	  </summary>
   </FAQ>
   
   <FAQ qid="Q1">
	  <summary>
		<p><i> What happens when a plane is returned in worse condition than when it left?</i></p>
		<p> We will inspect the plane and determine if the renter is responsible or not.</p>
	  </summary>
   </FAQ>
   
    <FAQ qid="Q1">
	  <summary>
		<p><i> Where do I go to look at planes that can be rented?</i></p>
		<p> You can see all the planes available for rent at the Product page.</p>
	  </summary>
   </FAQ>
   
    <FAQ qid="Q1">
	  <summary>
		<p><i> How do I remove a bid on a plane rental?</i></p>
		<p> You can cancel a bid from your account page as long as the bidding has not ended on the plane.</p>
	  </summary>
   </FAQ>
   
	<FAQ qid="Q1">
	  <summary>
		<p><i> How much is it to rent a plane?</i></p>
		<p> You can check our packages here for our base pricing, however; bidding will take place notified through our website.</p>
	  </summary>
   </FAQ>
   
   <FAQ qid="Q1">
	  <summary>
		<p><i> How do I know when my plane has been rented out to someone?</i></p>
		<p> We will send you an email telling you that your plane was been rented with the person who is renting’s info.</p>
	  </summary>
   </FAQ>
   
   <FAQ qid="Q1">
	  <summary>
		<p><i> How do I modify my trip?</i></p>
		<p> You can modify the trip at the account page, however; we only cover the specifics of your jet rental, please notify any lodging/activites via their websites.</p>
	  </summary>
   </FAQ>
</FAQs>